emailhelpr.com 2018-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Gmail Login and Gmail Sign in Information

Our Commitment To Your Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

DISCLAIMER: Google and Gmail is NOT affiliated with EmailHelpr.com and is a trademark of Google Inc. aka Alphabet Inc. 

DoubleClick DART Cookie 

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on emailhelpr.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

emailhelpr.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. emailhelpr.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. 

Our Commitment To Data Security 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy 

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18. Under our Terms of Service, children under 18 are no allowed to access our service. 

Collection of Personal Information 

On visiting this site, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Importantly, IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Links to third party websites 

We have included links on this site for your reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. 

Email Marketing Promotion & 3rd Party Ads 

Users that connect to us through social login or otherwise opt into our email newsletter form expressly give their permission to email market promotions & 3rd party advertisements 

Alterations to this Privacy Statement 

The content of this statement may be altered at any time –
